Chandler, Mon, there's only one
banana-nut muffin left.
I ordered mine first.
Yeah, but I'm so much faster.
Give it to me.
No.
Give it to me!
Okay, you can have it.
There you go. Enjoy your coffee.
That was there when I got here.
Hey, you'll never guess
who's coming to New York.
Quick, tell us before he swallows.
Ryan, that guy I dated
who's in the Navy.
You went out with a guy in the Navy?
I met him while playing guitar
in the park.
Ryan threw in saltwater taffy
because he didn't have change.
Is that when you wrote
"Saltwater Taffy Man"?
No, he's my submarine guy.
He resurfaces every couple years...
...and we have an amazing
three days together.
Only this time, he's coming for 2 weeks.
Two whole weeks, which means "yea"!
So this guy goes down
for, like, two years at a time?
That'll teach you to lick my muffin.
Hi.
Oh, no. What happened?
I just spoke to Carol.
Ben's got chickenpox.
Oh, no.
Yeah, so if you haven't had it,
chances are you'll get it.
-I've had it.
-Had it.
I've never had it. I feel so left out.
Oh, look!
The One With the Chicken Pox
Honey, you made the bed again.
I told you, you don't have to do that.
This isn't camp.
Then I guess the panty raid last night
was totally uncalled for.
I'm taking a shower. Today I'll
sing Jim Croce's "Leroy Brown."
Hey, Mon, I have a question.
Is Leroy the baddest man
in the whole damn town...
...or the fattest man?
The baddest. Otherwise, the song
would be "Fat, Fat Leroy Brown."
What are you doing?
I'm just waiting for you, sweetie.
Are you remaking the bed?
I'm sorry. The way you did it,
it was just fine.
Then you're redoing it
because...?
You'll think I'm crazy.
You're pretty much
running that risk either way.
Okay. You see...
...the duvet tag shouldn't be
at the top left corner...
...it should be at the
bottom right corner.
-That's not so crazy.
-I'm just easing you in.
All right.
You see these little flower blossoms?
They should be facing up not down...
...because the head of the bed
is where the sun would be.
You don't love me anymore, do you?
Actually, if it's possible,
I love you more.
Really?
Wow. Well, then, come on!
I wanna show you how to fold
the toilet paper into a point.
If you need something
to hold you over...
...I can get you a job here
as an entry-level processor.
Don't you need experience?
It's not hard to learn.
As for people realizing you don't know
what you're doing, you're an actor.
Act like a processor,
people will think you're a processor.
Here's this morning's projections.
Thanks.
Scott Alexander, Joey Tribbiani.
Joey is a fellow processor.
No kidding?
I process. People want the processing,
I'm the one they call.
-Where do you work?
-Well, I'm in between things.
You know, one day you're processing,
the next day...
...you're not so much
processing anymore.
I told Joey about the opening
in Fleischman's group.
Fleischman's group.
Whatever you do,
don't touch his sandwiches.
Are all you processors dorks?
This lipstick looks just great on you.
You look fabulous.
You really do.
Yeah, are you sure?
Really?
See, you look beautiful.
For God sakes, dim the lights.
I'm hideous!
It's gonna be okay.
Ryan's been underwater.
He's just gonna be glad you don't
have barnacles on your butt.
Come in.
Hey, baby, I'm back
Hey, Ryan. What's up?
What's going on?
No, no.
You have to stay back.
I have the pox!
Chicken or small?
Chicken, which is so ironic
considering I'm a vegetarian.
-Why aren't you home in bed?
-My grandmother's never had chickenpox.
Please tell me you have, because
oh, my God, I forgot how cute you are.
I'm sorry, I never had them.
If I had one wish,
I'd go back to when I was 7...
...when Jimmy Hauser had chickenpox,
and rub that kid all over my face.
Yeah, or you could wish
that I didn't have them now.
Can I see your face?
No. You don't wanna see a face
covered with pox.
It could be lox, I wouldn't care.
And you hate fish.
So sweet. All right.
Okay, all right.
You can see.
This is me.
Sorry!
I am scary!
The lightening was
an unfortunate coincidence.
You look lovely!
Lovely!
I hate this.
I had the most amazing
two weeks planned for us.
And everything I had in mind,
we had to be a lot closer than this.
I've spent the last eight months
in a steel tube with men...
...thinking about this moment.
I am not gonna let a bunch...
...of itchy spots stand between us.
Okay. This is the most
romantic disease I've ever had.
-How's the first day?
-Good. It's like you said.
It's putting numbers
from one column into another.
There you go.
And everybody's nice. I just had
a good talk with that lady Jeannie.
Jeannie? The head of
East Coast operations, Jeannie?
Turns out our kids go
to the same school.
Yeah. Small world, huh?
Weird world.
Your kids?
I figure my character has kids.
There isn't a part of that sentence
I don't need explained.
When you're acting, you need
to think about that stuff.
My character,
Joseph the processing guy...
... has two little girls,
Ashley and Brittany.
Ashley copies everything
Brittany does.
Well, invisible kids
can be that way sometimes.
You know, Joseph and his wife, Karen,
are thinking of having a third kid.
You know what?
Just did.
That's some pretty powerful
imaginary sperm you must have there.
IKnow what makes the itching worse?
That you don't stop talking about it?
-Fine.
-Let's just play, okay?
Good, okay.
Here we go, double sixes.
Here we go....
Come to Mama.
Getting ready to roll the dice....
What are you doing?
Are you scratching?
No. This is what I do
for luck, okay?
You're scratching.
Give me the dice.
-Give me the dice.
-No! Here. There!
Look, double sixes!
We can't scratch. We'll scar.
I can't stop thinking about it.
It's just so hard.
I wanna grab these houses
and rub them all over my body.
-No!
-Give it!
Come on!
You know you want it.
You know you want it too.
Let's just be bad.
It'll feel so good.
Come on.
Oh, God, help me.
-Oh, yeah.
-Okay, good. Now do me.
Do my back.
Oh, come on. Harder!
There you go.
-Don't move.
-Why?
-What are you...?
Stop that.
Stop that right now.
I might've expected this of Phoebe.
But, Ryan, you're a military man.
You and Milton have to join us
on the boat. Bring the kids.
We'll make a day of it.
That sounds lovely.
We'll have to set it up.
I better get back.
Hope the baby feels better.
Thanks.
-Bye-bye, Jeannie.
-Bye-bye, Joseph.
What a phony.
You'll teach her a lesson when she
steps off the dock onto nothing.
-Hey, Mr. Douglas.
-Sir.
Bing, I got your memo. We're not gonna
see the report until next Friday?
My group wants to spend
the holiday with family.
I have a family.
I'm gonna be here.
Yeah, Bing.
What's that about?
It's about cutting them
a little slack for morale.
Look, I can get some
rough numbers by Wednesday.
Rough numbers?
This company wasn't built
on rough numbers. Right, Mr. Douglas?
Have the final numbers
on my desk by Tuesday.
If you say so, sir.
Joseph's good, isn't he?
I'm going to kill you.
Hey, I just figured Joseph's
the kind of guy who likes to mix it up.
You know, get in there,
ruffle some feathers.
Why?
Look, I'm sorry,
but that's what Joseph does.
Okay? If you try to pull something...
... he'll call you on it.
"What are you trying to pull?"
he'll say.
Duct tape.
Was I supposed to bring something too?
This is for the scratchy twins.
I taped oven mitts to their hands.
You're strict.
Well, it's for their own good.
You know, I like the way you have
efficiently folded this tab under.
See, in a tape emergency you could
shave valuable seconds off your time.
Exactly!
God, I love that I can be
totally neurotic around you now.
Tell me the truth.
Don't you like having everything
on your desk perpendicular?
If it's not a right angle,
it is a wrong angle.
-Very good.
-Thank you.
Tomorrow, I'm gonna do your clocks.
You're gonna do what to my clocks?
Set them to my time.
I'm confused.
I thought we shared time.
No. See, in my bedroom
I set my clock six minutes fast.
Wanna know why?
Because it's in a slightly different
time zone than the kitchen?
Forget it.
No, come on, tell me.
-You don't understand.
-Come on.
You don't have any obsessive things.
No, that's not true.
Oh, yeah?
Tell me one of yours.
One of my things is
I always separate my sweat socks...
...from my dress socks.
What if they get mixed up?
Boy, I would just....
I would freak out.
You would not.
I can't believe this.
I hate this. You're too normal.
I can't believe you
don't have a "thing."
My boyfriend doesn't have a "thing."
See, if anyone overheard that,
I didn't come off well.
-Mr. Douglas is looking for you.
-Why is Mr. Douglas looking for me?
He suspects you dropped the ball
on the Lender project.
Why? Why does he suspect that?
At first, he thought it was Joseph...
...but after he asked Joseph about it,
turns out it was you.
-Anyway, I thought you should know.
-All right. That's it.
Look, Joey...
... I realize this is the role
of a lifetime for you...
...and if I could just fire Joseph,
I would. But that's not possible.
So I have to let you both go.
What? Everybody loves Joseph.
I don't. I hate Joseph.
I think he's a brown-nosing suck-up.
You can't fire Joseph.
He's not in your department.
All right, okay.
So I can't fire Joseph...
... but I can sleep with his wife.
Not Karen!
Yeah, I'm thinking about
having an affair with her.
You know what?
I just did.
What the hell are you doing?
Oh, it's not me.
It's my character!
Chandie.
The rogue processor who seduces
his coworkers' wives...
...and then laughs about it.
In fact, I have her panties
right there in my drawer!
-Really?
-No, freak show, she's fictional!
Take it easy.
If it means that much to you,
I'll go find something else.
Thank you.
It's just that
I'm gonna miss Joseph.
I liked him. His wife.
She was hot.
Please take these off.
I swear I won't scratch.
No, sorry, hon.
Monica's orders.
Well, that wasn't easy.
Okay, dinner's on.
There's a peach cobbler
warming in the oven.
So the plate's gonna be hot, but that
shouldn't be a problem for you.
All right, you kids.
Bye, now.
-Bye.
-Oh, look, look.
A low-budget puppet show.
A shame you can't see
what finger I'm holding up.
-Wine?
-Please.
-Spilled some.
-I got it.
You look beautiful tonight.
What?
Sorry.
You look beautiful.
You know what? That's it.
That's it.
Oh, yes.
Good.
You guys, did you?
Monica...
...wake up.
What's up?
I thought of a thing.
Yeah?
I have to sleep, have to,
on this side of the bed.
No. You have to sleep
on this side of the bed...
... because I have to sleep
on this side of the bed.
Or so I would have you believe.
So you have a side of the bed.
Everybody has a side of the bed.
Hey, come on. You haven't
heard my reason yet.
All right, go on.
I have to sleep on the west side...
... because I grew up in California...
...and otherwise...
...the ocean would be on the wrong side.
Oh, my God.
You're a freak!
How about that?
Where're you shipping off to?
I really can't say.
Do you have nuclear weapons onboard?
I can't say.
Do you get to look through
a periscope thingy?
I'm sorry, but I can't say.
Wow, it's neat learning
about submarines.
-I better not miss my flight.
-I'll walk you out.
-Bye, Ryan.
-Pleasure. Take care.
So do you think we could get you
one of those uniform things?
You like that, do you?
Oh, yeah.
I'll make some calls.
Can you believe that's how
we spent our two weeks?
We didn't do the romantic
things I'd planned...
...Iike having a picnic in Central Park
and coffee at Central Perk.
Oh, I just got that!
Taxi!
Bye, you.
I'm sorry, we're
Hey, sailor.
Is this what you had in mind?
I'll say.
I'm shipping out tomorrow.
Well, then...
...we better make this night count.
Wait, I forgot to turn off
the cappuccino machine.
Anchors aweigh.
Oh, wait, wait!
My purse, my purse!
I forgot to turn off the bathroom light.
Why don't I just meet you upstairs?
Honey!